[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "que",
    "questionDetails": "Así que respeta las limitaciones que ese sobreviviente pueda tener.",
    "answer": "that, which, who",
    "answerDetails": "So respect those limitations that that survivor may have."
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "no",
    "questionDetails": "Tratar los síntomas y no la causa.",
    "answer": "not, does it",
    "answerDetails": "Treating the symptoms and not the cause."
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "a",
    "questionDetails": "Puede ser que sea lo que me pasó a mi.",
    "answer": "to",
    "answerDetails": "Maybe that’s what happened to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "de",
    "questionDetails": "Este tipo de libro.",
    "answer": "of, to, in",
    "answerDetails": "This type of book."
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "la",
    "questionDetails": "La parte superior de un autobús.",
    "answer": "the, it",
    "answerDetails": "The top of a bus."
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "y",
    "questionDetails": "Y te preocupa rías.",
    "answer": "and",
    "answerDetails": "And you would worry."
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "me",
    "questionDetails": "Voy a quitarme la chaqueta porque tengo mucho calor.",
    "answer": "my",
    "answerDetails": "I’m going to take off my jacket because I’m really hot."
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "es",
    "questionDetails": "Me gusta esta cafetera. Es fácil de usar.",
    "answer": "it is, you are, he is",
    "answerDetails": "I like this coffee maker. It is easy to use."
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "lo",
    "questionDetails": "No tengo planes establecidos y estoy abierto a lo.",
    "answer": "what, it",
    "answerDetails": "I have no set plans and am open to whatevs."
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "qué",
    "answer": "that"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "el",
    "questionDetails": "Él era el prospecto de piano joven caliente en el jazz.",
    "answer": "the",
    "answerDetails": "He was the hot young piano prospect in jazz."
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "en",
    "questionDetails": "Ella está en un shock.",
    "answer": "in, on to, with",
    "answerDetails": "She’s in for a shock."
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "por",
    "questionDetails": "¿Te pagan por hora o por trabajo?",
    "answer": "by, for, of",
    "answerDetails": "Are you paid by the hour or by the job?"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "se",
    "questionDetails": "¿Por qué están pidiendo el pago? ¡ Ya se lo di!.",
    "answer": "them, himself",
    "answerDetails": "Why are they asking for the payment? I already gave it to them!."
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "con",
    "questionDetails": "Consigo.",
    "answer": "with, to, by",
    "answerDetails": "With himself/herself."
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "un",
    "questionDetails": "Te dejé un poco de dinero.",
    "answer": "a, an",
    "answerDetails": "I left you a few bucks."
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "ya",
    "questionDetails": "La película ya está empezando.",
    "answer": "now, anymore, yet",
    "answerDetails": "The movie is beginning now."
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "para",
    "questionDetails": "Se embarcó en un avión para Santiago.",
    "answer": "for, to, by",
    "answerDetails": "She got on a plane for Santiago."
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "mi",
    "questionDetails": "Necesito volver a ordenar mi vida.",
    "answer": "my",
    "answerDetails": "I need to get my life back on track."
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "una",
    "questionDetails": "Me gustaría una manzana.",
    "answer": "an, one",
    "answerDetails": "I’d like an apple."
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "está",
    "answer": "this"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "los",
    "questionDetails": "Me gustan todos los vestidos de la tienda.",
    "answer": "the",
    "answerDetails": "I like all the dresses in the store."
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "si",
    "questionDetails": "Si te gusta voy a poner en una palabra para usted.",
    "answer": "if, whether",
    "answerDetails": "If you like I’ll put in a word for you."
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "las",
    "questionDetails": "Las horas de trabajo en la herrería son inaceptables.",
    "answer": "the",
    "answerDetails": "The working hours at the forge are quite unacceptable."
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "más",
    "questionDetails": "Tendríamos que resumir la nota lo más posible, porque no va a caber en el espacio.",
    "answer": "as much as, any longer, most",
    "answerDetails": "We should summarize the note as much as possible, because otherwise it won’t fit in the space."
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "del",
    "questionDetails": "Hay muchos pájaros en las ramas del árbol.",
    "answer": "of the, in the, from the",
    "answerDetails": "There are many birds in the branches of the tree."
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "yo",
    "questionDetails": "Amo los cachorros.-Yo también.",
    "answer": "me",
    "answerDetails": "I love puppies.-Me, Too."
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "pero",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo lo he visto una vez, pero lo he escuchado muchas veces.",
    "answer": "but, only",
    "answerDetails": "I’ve only seen him once, but I’ve heard him many times."
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "le",
    "questionDetails": "Le diré a dónde ir.",
    "answer": "you, it",
    "answerDetails": "I’ll tell you where to go."
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "eso",
    "questionDetails": "Tráeme eso.",
    "answer": "that, right on",
    "answerDetails": "Bring me that."
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "todo",
    "questionDetails": "Ella era elocuente, ella era divertida-me pareció que tenía todo.",
    "answer": "everything",
    "answerDetails": "She was articulate, she was fun—it seemed to me she had everything."
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "como",
    "questionDetails": "Así que como pueden ver, es una linda máquina.",
    "answer": "as, like, such as",
    "answerDetails": "So as you can see, really nice machine."
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "muy",
    "questionDetails": "Muy bien, Sr., ¿eso será todo?",
    "answer": "very, highly, really",
    "answerDetails": "Very good, sir, will that be all?"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "su",
    "questionDetails": "Mal humor ella la arrojó en su cara.",
    "answer": "her",
    "answerDetails": "Peevishly she flung her on her face."
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "o",
    "questionDetails": "O quizás sea al contrario.",
    "answer": "or",
    "answerDetails": "Or maybe it’s the other way around."
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "al",
    "questionDetails": "Vamos al centro comercial después de Clases.",
    "answer": "to the, on, when",
    "answerDetails": "We’re going to the shopping mall after class."
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "así",
    "questionDetails": "Hazlo así.",
    "answer": "so, thus, that way",
    "answerDetails": "Do it so."
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "esta",
    "questionDetails": "Esta vez, parece que sí.",
    "answer": "this",
    "answerDetails": "This time, it seems there is."
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "son",
    "questionDetails": "Unos Son valientes y otros son cobardes.",
    "answer": "some are, you are, you all are",
    "answerDetails": "Some are brave and others are cowards."
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "te",
    "questionDetails": "Te veré allí.",
    "answer": "you",
    "answerDetails": "I’ll see you there."
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "bien",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Bien hecho!.",
    "answer": "well, good, okay",
    "answerDetails": "Well done!."
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "porque",
    "questionDetails": "Lo hicimos porque sentimos que nuestro deber.",
    "answer": "because",
    "answerDetails": "We did it because we felt it our duty."
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "nada",
    "questionDetails": "Si usted piensa que era barro, usted no ha visto nada todavía.",
    "answer": "nothing, anything, none",
    "answerDetails": "If you think that was muddy, you ain’t seen nothing yet."
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "sé",
    "questionDetails": "Yo sé lo que tenemos que hacer.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "I know what we need to do."
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "hacer",
    "questionDetails": "Papá tendría que hacer con un coche viejo.",
    "answer": "make, work, take",
    "answerDetails": "Dad would have to make do with an old car."
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "tiene",
    "questionDetails": "¿Dónde está mi chaqueta?-Marcelo la tiene.",
    "answer": "has it, you have",
    "answerDetails": "Where’s my jacket?-Marcelo has it."
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "hay",
    "questionDetails": "Hay un circo en la ciudad.",
    "answer": "there is, is there, are there any",
    "answerDetails": "There is a circus in town."
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "ahora",
    "questionDetails": "Que han estado casados 4 años ahora.",
    "answer": "now",
    "answerDetails": "They’ve been married four years now."
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "ser",
    "questionDetails": "Que debe ser él en la puerta.",
    "answer": "be, make",
    "answerDetails": "That must be him at the door."
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "mucho",
    "questionDetails": "¿Vienes mucho a este café a estudiar?",
    "answer": "much, lot, long",
    "answerDetails": "Do you come to this cafe to study much?"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "cuando",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando uno tiene sed, todo sabe mejor.",
    "answer": "when",
    "answerDetails": "When one is thirsty, it always tastes better."
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "también",
    "questionDetails": "Un lingüista brillante, también estaba interesado en la botánica.",
    "answer": "also",
    "answerDetails": "A brilliant linguist, he was also interested in botany."
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "vez",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que me perdone esto una vez.",
    "answer": "once",
    "answerDetails": "I hope you’ll forgive me this once."
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "question": "sí",
    "questionDetails": "Yo le conocía, sí.",
    "answer": "yes, okay, do",
    "answerDetails": "I used to know him, yes."
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "nos",
    "questionDetails": "Nos permiten que el pensamiento vaya muy rápido.",
    "answer": "us, we",
    "answerDetails": "This allows us to think way quicker."
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "ver",
    "questionDetails": "Ver or véase pág. 50.",
    "answer": "see, view, watch",
    "answerDetails": "See page 50."
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "question": "esto",
    "questionDetails": "Escucha esto.",
    "answer": "this, uh",
    "answerDetails": "Listen to this."
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "question": "este",
    "questionDetails": "Hubo un caso judicial resultante de este incidente.",
    "answer": "this, east",
    "answerDetails": "There was a court case resulting from this incident."
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "question": "algo",
    "questionDetails": "Preguntó si había algo que podía hacer.",
    "answer": "anything, somewhat, rather",
    "answerDetails": "He inquired whether there was anything he could do."
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "question": "ese",
    "questionDetails": "Le permití gastar todo ese dinero en mí.",
    "answer": "that",
    "answerDetails": "I let him spend all that money on me."
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "question": "ahí",
    "questionDetails": "Ahí estás, eso será £ 3, 80 por favor.",
    "answer": "there",
    "answerDetails": "There you are—that’ll be £3.80 please."
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "question": "mejor",
    "questionDetails": "Usted sólo tendrá que hacer lo mejor de la situación.",
    "answer": "best, better",
    "answerDetails": "You’ll just have to make the best of the situation."
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "question": "dos",
    "questionDetails": "Necesito comprar dos libros para mi clase de literatura.",
    "answer": "two",
    "answerDetails": "I need to buy two books for my literature class."
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "question": "cómo",
    "questionDetails": "No sé cómo hacer esto.",
    "answer": "how, what",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t know how to do this."
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "question": "vamos",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Vamos! ¡ Aún podemos ganar el partido!.",
    "answer": "come on, go for it",
    "answerDetails": "Come on! We can still win the game!."
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "question": "tengo",
    "questionDetails": "Si tienes 25, ¿verdad?-¿Que si tengo 25? No, tengo 30.",
    "answer": "am i, i am",
    "answerDetails": "You are 25, aren’t you?-Am I 25? No, I’m 30."
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "question": "esa",
    "questionDetails": "Esa es su esposa allí.",
    "answer": "that",
    "answerDetails": "That’s his wife over there."
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "question": "tiempo",
    "questionDetails": "El aeródromo estaba en uso todo el tiempo.",
    "answer": "time, period, day",
    "answerDetails": "The airfield was in use all the time."
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "question": "día",
    "questionDetails": "El Zorro entró en el gallinero durante el día.",
    "answer": "daylight, daytime",
    "answerDetails": "The Fox got into the henhouse in daylight."
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "question": "voy",
    "questionDetails": "¿Dónde te entrenas?-Voy a un gimnasio nuevo cerca de mi casa.",
    "answer": "i am going, i am coming",
    "answerDetails": "Where do you work out?-I am going to a new gym near my house."
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "question": "bueno",
    "questionDetails": "Bueno, como iba diciendo…",
    "answer": "well, good, kind",
    "answerDetails": "Well, as I was saying…"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "question": "fue",
    "questionDetails": "¿Quién es Alejandro?-Él fue mi primer Amor.",
    "answer": "he was, was it, you were",
    "answerDetails": "Who’s Alejandro?-He was my first love."
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "question": "puede",
    "questionDetails": "¿Puede recomendar buenas acciones para comprar?",
    "answer": "can you, he can, he may",
    "answerDetails": "Can you recommend any good stocks to buy?"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "question": "todos",
    "questionDetails": "Todos los hombres.",
    "answer": "all, everyone, everybody",
    "answerDetails": "All men."
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "question": "era",
    "questionDetails": "¿Era difícil vivir en un ambiente tan caótico?",
    "answer": "was it, age, you were",
    "answerDetails": "Was it hard to live in such a chaotic environment?"
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "question": "hace",
    "questionDetails": "Volvió a su país hace algún tiempo.",
    "answer": "ago, does it, makes it",
    "answerDetails": "She returned to her country some time ago."
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "question": "les",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que les guste.",
    "answer": "them",
    "answerDetails": "I hope you like them."
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "question": "va",
    "questionDetails": "Esta es nuestra primera cita. Si va bien, nos volveremos a ver.",
    "answer": "it goes, she is going",
    "answerDetails": "This is our first date. If it goes well we’ll meet again."
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "question": "pasa",
    "questionDetails": "Pasa mucho.",
    "answer": "it happens, after you, raisin",
    "answerDetails": "It happens a lot."
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "question": "siempre",
    "questionDetails": "Si el matrimonio no funciona, siempre podemos divorciarnos.",
    "answer": "always",
    "answerDetails": "If the marriage doesn’t work out, we can always get divorced."
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "question": "otra",
    "questionDetails": "Me encantan estas paletas. ¿Puedo tomar otra?",
    "answer": "another",
    "answerDetails": "I love these popsicles. Can I have another?"
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "question": "uno",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo queda uno.",
    "answer": "one",
    "answerDetails": "There’s only one left."
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "question": "estoy",
    "questionDetails": "¿Estás contento con el Servicio Sr. Jones?-¿Estoy sonriendo? Esto no es una sonrisa.",
    "answer": "am i",
    "answerDetails": "Are you happy with the service Mr. Jones?-Am I smiling? This is not a smile."
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "question": "quiero",
    "questionDetails": "Lo quiero, pero no le intereso yo.",
    "answer": "i want him, i love him, i love her",
    "answerDetails": "I want him, but he isn’t interested in me."
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "question": "estar",
    "questionDetails": "Hay que estar juntos.",
    "answer": "be",
    "answerDetails": "It is necessary to be together."
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "question": "están",
    "answer": "some are"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "question": "hasta",
    "questionDetails": "Hasta mañana, no.",
    "answer": "until, even, down to",
    "answerDetails": "Not until tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "question": "estaba",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando llegué a casa de mis padres, él estaba en la cocina preparando la cena.",
    "answer": "he was",
    "answerDetails": "When I arrived at my parents’, he was in the kitchen making dinner."
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "question": "sin",
    "questionDetails": "Lo hizo todo sola, sin ayuda de nadie.",
    "answer": "no",
    "answerDetails": "She did it all on her own, with no help at all."
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "question": "gracias",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Gracias por traerme a casa!.",
    "answer": "thanks",
    "answerDetails": "Thanks for the ride home!."
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "question": "él",
    "questionDetails": "Él la escuchó con asombro.",
    "answer": "he, him",
    "answerDetails": "He heard her with astonishment."
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "question": "quién",
    "questionDetails": "¿con quién se casó?",
    "answer": "whom",
    "answerDetails": "Whom did he marry?"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "question": "vida",
    "questionDetails": "Cubitos de hielo tintados en cristales. “Esta es la vida”, dijo.",
    "answer": "life",
    "answerDetails": "Ice cubes clinked in Crystal glasses. ‘This is the life,’ she said."
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "question": "dónde",
    "questionDetails": "Dónde está él?",
    "answer": "where",
    "answerDetails": "Where are they now?"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "question": "cosas",
    "questionDetails": "Este fin de semana voy a recoger mis cosas de la casa de mi exnovia.",
    "answer": "things, stuff",
    "answerDetails": "I am going to pick up my things from my ex-girlfiend’s place this weekend."
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "question": "creo",
    "questionDetails": "Mi madre dice que creo problemas en todos los sitios a los que voy.",
    "answer": "i make, i believe you",
    "answerDetails": "My mother says I make problems wherever I go."
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "question": "tenemos",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos problemas para obtener acceso a su cuenta. Por favor, vuelva a intentar más tarde.",
    "answer": "we are having",
    "answerDetails": "We are having trouble accessing your account. Please, try again later."
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "question": "otro",
    "questionDetails": "¿En qué otro lugar hay una estación de tren en esta ciudad?",
    "answer": "else",
    "answerDetails": "Where else is there a train station in this city?"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "question": "aquí",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy en el restaurante, pero no los veo.-Estamos aquí por la barra.",
    "answer": "over",
    "answerDetails": "I’m at the restaurant, but I don’t see you.-We’re over here by the bar."
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "question": "mí",
    "questionDetails": "No te puedes arriesgar, ni siquiera por mí.",
    "answer": "me",
    "answerDetails": "You cannot risk yourself, even for me."
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "ni",
    "questionDetails": "Ni fuma ni bebe or.",
    "answer": "nor, neither",
    "answerDetails": "He neither drinks nor smokes."
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "question": "solo",
    "questionDetails": "El quedarse callado solo los hace mas fuertes.",
    "answer": "only, just, alone",
    "answerDetails": "Silence only makes them stronger."
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "question": "nunca",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Nunca más!.",
    "answer": "never",
    "answerDetails": "Never again!."
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "question": "verdad",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos este llamamiento constante para oraciones más duras y la verdad en la sentencia.",
    "answer": "truth, right, am i",
    "answerDetails": "We have this constant call for tougher sentences and truth in sentencing."
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "question": "nosotros",
    "questionDetails": "Le pedimos que viniera con nosotros.",
    "answer": "us",
    "answerDetails": "We asked him to come with us."
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "question": "tres",
    "questionDetails": "Tienen tres días para irse.",
    "answer": "three",
    "answerDetails": "You have three days to get out."
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "question": "estás",
    "questionDetails": "Noté que estás usando titanio.",
    "answer": "‘re, re",
    "answerDetails": "I notice you’re using titanium."
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "question": "puedo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Puedo ver esa revista por un momento?",
    "answer": "can i, may i, i am able",
    "answerDetails": "Can I see that magazine for a minute?"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "question": "ir",
    "answer": "ride"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "question": "tener",
    "questionDetails": "Ella va a tener un bebé.",
    "answer": "have",
    "answerDetails": "She’s going to have a baby."
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "question": "tu",
    "questionDetails": "Dime, hermosa doncella, cómo podré ganar tu Amor.",
    "answer": "thy",
    "answerDetails": "Tell me, fair maiden, how I may win thy love."
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "question": "gente",
    "questionDetails": "Él es mucho un hombre de la gente.",
    "answer": "people",
    "answerDetails": "He is very much a man of the people."
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "question": "decir",
    "questionDetails": "¿Jura decir la verdad?",
    "answer": "tell",
    "answerDetails": "Do you swear to tell the truth?"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "question": "estamos",
    "answer": "we are"
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "question": "mis",
    "questionDetails": "El cine era en su origen de mis tíos.",
    "answer": "my",
    "answerDetails": "The cinema originally belonged to my aunt and uncle."
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "question": "soy",
    "questionDetails": "¿Quién eres?-¿Quién soy yo? Soy el presidente de tu universidad.",
    "answer": "am i, i am",
    "answerDetails": "Who are you?-Who am I? I’m the president of your college."
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "question": "entonces",
    "questionDetails": "No podemos usar ese nombre para nuestro restaurante.-Entonces, ¿qué piensas de llamarlo “El Agave”?",
    "answer": "in that case",
    "answerDetails": "We can’t use that name for our restaurant.-In that case, what do you think of calling it “El Agave”?"
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "question": "casa",
    "questionDetails": "Las Casas de Lancaster y York pelearon en la guerra de las Dos Rosas.",
    "answer": "house, company, place",
    "answerDetails": "The Houses of Lancaster and York battled in the War of the Roses."
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "question": "después",
    "questionDetails": "Ella miró después de él.",
    "answer": "after, later, next",
    "answerDetails": "She stared after him."
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "question": "poco",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos un poco de ayuda de un esquema de entrenamiento.",
    "answer": "little, some, slightly",
    "answerDetails": "We got a little help from a training scheme."
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "question": "favor",
    "questionDetails": "¡ No te olvides de darle las gracias por ofrecerse a hacerte el favor!.",
    "answer": "favour",
    "answerDetails": "Don’t forget to thank him for offering to do you a favour!."
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "question": "tan",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy tan hambriento. Llevo horas sin comer.",
    "answer": "so, such, just",
    "answerDetails": "I’m so hungry. I haven’t eaten in Hours."
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "question": "nadie",
    "questionDetails": "No había nadie allí.",
    "answer": "anyone, anybody, none",
    "answerDetails": "There wasn’t anyone there."
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "question": "antes",
    "questionDetails": "Trotando a través de la ciudad con guardias corriendo antes y detrás.",
    "answer": "before, first, earlier",
    "answerDetails": "Trotting through the city with guards running before and behind."
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "question": "años",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo 25 años.",
    "answer": "years old",
    "answerDetails": "I’m 25 years old."
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "question": "vas",
    "questionDetails": "Si vas al supermercado, acuérdate de comprar leche.",
    "answer": "you go, you are going",
    "answerDetails": "If you go to the grocery store, remember to buy milk."
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "question": "van",
    "questionDetails": "Los niños van al parque todos los días después de la escuela.",
    "answer": "(they) go",
    "answerDetails": "The children go to the park every day after school."
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "question": "mismo",
    "questionDetails": "Que ha trabajado en el mismo lugar durante unos cuantos años.",
    "answer": "same, very, as much",
    "answerDetails": "He’s worked at the same place for quite a few years."
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "question": "hoy",
    "questionDetails": "Pero hoy, no tenemos tiempo para esto.",
    "answer": "today",
    "answerDetails": "But today, we have no time for this."
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "question": "desde",
    "questionDetails": "La peor caída de la propiedad desde la guerra.",
    "answer": "since, from",
    "answerDetails": "The worst property slump since the war."
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "question": "quiere",
    "questionDetails": "Es su hijo y lo quiere, de modo que lo va a apoyar cueste lo que cueste.",
    "answer": "he loves him",
    "answerDetails": "He’s his son, and he loves him, so he’ll support him, whatever it takes."
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "question": "sus",
    "questionDetails": "Que hagan sus propias llamadas.",
    "answer": "their",
    "answerDetails": "Have them make their own calls."
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "question": "toda",
    "questionDetails": "El agua es la fuente de toda vida.",
    "answer": "all, whole, entire",
    "answerDetails": "Water is the source of all life."
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "question": "cosa",
    "questionDetails": "En Denver este fin de semana se pueden hacer un montón de cosas.",
    "answer": "thing",
    "answerDetails": "There are a lot of things to do this weekend in Denver."
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "question": "sea",
    "questionDetails": "Es probable que la parálisis sea permanente.",
    "answer": "be, ‘s, either",
    "answerDetails": "The paralysis will likely be permanent."
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "question": "momento",
    "questionDetails": "El momento de la verdad para la mayoría de los niños alemanes viene al final del grado 4.",
    "answer": "moment, point, minute",
    "answerDetails": "The moment of truth for most German children comes at the end of Grade 4."
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "question": "menos",
    "questionDetails": "Que este es un estereotipo positivo lo hace no menos un estereotipo.",
    "answer": "less, least, fewer",
    "answerDetails": "That this is a positive stereotype makes it no less a stereotype."
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "question": "cuenta",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo una cuenta corriente y una cuenta de ahorro con el mismo banco.",
    "answer": "account, check, he tells",
    "answerDetails": "I have a checking account and a savings account at the same bank."
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "question": "da",
    "questionDetails": "Le gusta llevar ese traje. Le da seguridad en sí misma.",
    "answer": "it gives",
    "answerDetails": "She likes to wear that outfit. It gives her confidence."
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "question": "ella",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Es ella!.",
    "answer": "her",
    "answerDetails": "It’s her!."
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "question": "claro",
    "questionDetails": "La razón de la evasividad de Pedro fue de repente tan claro como el día.",
    "answer": "clear, light, pale",
    "answerDetails": "The reason for Peter’s evasiveness was suddenly as clear as day."
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "question": "mañana",
    "questionDetails": "Un toque de luz acercada mostró que la mañana estaba en su camino.",
    "answer": "morning",
    "answerDetails": "A hint of steely light showed that morning was on its way."
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "question": "días",
    "questionDetails": "Tienen tres días para irse.",
    "answer": "days, morning",
    "answerDetails": "You have three days to get out."
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "question": "unos",
    "questionDetails": "¿Tienes unos minutos después de la clase para hablar?",
    "answer": "few",
    "answerDetails": "Do you have a few minutes after class to chat?"
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "question": "sabe",
    "questionDetails": "No quiero que nadie sepa que me despidieron.-Lisa lo sabe, pero no se lo dirá a nadie.",
    "answer": "knows",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t want anyone to know that I was fired.-Lisa knows, but she won’t tell anyone."
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "question": "dije",
    "questionDetails": "Dije la verdad. Nunca miento.",
    "answer": "i told",
    "answerDetails": "I told the truth. I never lie."
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "question": "dice",
    "questionDetails": "¿No te divertiste con mi hermana? Me dice que no la volviste a llamar.",
    "answer": "she tells, says it",
    "answerDetails": "Did you not have fun with my sister? She tells me that you didn’t call her back."
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "question": "tenía",
    "questionDetails": "La cirugía debió posponerse porque tenía una infección.",
    "answer": "he had",
    "answerDetails": "The surgery had to be postponed because he had an infection."
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "question": "ha",
    "questionDetails": "Ha conocido a mucha gente viajando.",
    "answer": "you have",
    "answerDetails": "You have met a lot of people by traveling."
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "question": "hablar",
    "questionDetails": "Alguien tendrá que hablar con Lily.",
    "answer": "talk",
    "answerDetails": "Someone will have to talk to Lily."
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "question": "parece",
    "questionDetails": "Créeme, es mucho más fácil de lo que parece.",
    "answer": "it looks, it appears, she looks",
    "answerDetails": "Trust me, it’s a lot easier than it looks."
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "question": "gusta",
    "questionDetails": "¿Te gusta mi nuevo corte de pelo?-No, no me gusta. ¡ Me encanta!.",
    "answer": "like it",
    "answerDetails": "Do you like my new haircut?-No, I don’t like it. I love it!."
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "question": "alguien",
    "questionDetails": "Si quieres ser alguien, tienes que esforzarte.",
    "answer": "someone, somebody, anyone",
    "answerDetails": "If you want to be someone, you have to work at it."
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "question": "quería",
    "questionDetails": "Ella quería a su caballo más que a nadie en el mundo.",
    "answer": "she loved",
    "answerDetails": "She loved her horse more than anything in the world."
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "question": "muchas",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuántas personas vinieron a la fiesta?-Muchas.",
    "answer": "lot",
    "answerDetails": "How many people came to the party?-A lot."
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "question": "donde",
    "questionDetails": "Donde hay fe, hay esperanza.",
    "answer": "where",
    "answerDetails": "Where there is faith there is hope."
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "question": "había",
    "questionDetails": "Había muchas goteras en el techo.",
    "answer": "there were",
    "answerDetails": "There were many leaks in the ceiling."
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "question": "mundo",
    "questionDetails": "¿por qué en el mundo no te revelas antes?",
    "answer": "world, globe, life experience",
    "answerDetails": "Why in the world did you not reveal yourself sooner?"
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "question": "tanto",
    "questionDetails": "“Estoy cansada de bailar tanto”, dijo la novia.",
    "answer": "so much",
    "answerDetails": "“I’m tired from dancing so much,” said the bride."
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "question": "pasó",
    "questionDetails": "Puede ser que sea lo que me pasó a mi.",
    "answer": "happened, spent, passed",
    "answerDetails": "Maybe that’s what happened to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "question": "salir",
    "questionDetails": "Salir con alguien.",
    "answer": "go out, exit",
    "answerDetails": "To go out with somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "question": "veces",
    "questionDetails": "Las nubes están raras. Si cae algo, unas veces es lluvia y otras veces es Nieve.",
    "answer": "sometimes, at times",
    "answerDetails": "The clouds are weird. If something falls, sometimes it’s rain and other times it’s snow."
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "question": "viene",
    "questionDetails": "A mí me encanta Harry Potter, pero mi mamá cree que viene del diablo.",
    "answer": "it comes, he is coming, are you coming",
    "answerDetails": "I love Harry Potter, but my mom thinks it comes from the devil."
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "question": "todas",
    "questionDetails": "Todas las personas que conocí.",
    "answer": "all",
    "answerDetails": "All the people I met."
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "question": "dar",
    "questionDetails": "Te daré una aspirina para reducir tu temperatura.",
    "answer": "bring, allow",
    "answerDetails": "I’ll give you an aspirin to bring down your temperature."
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "question": "tal",
    "questionDetails": "Lo llevó a tal estado.",
    "answer": "such",
    "answerDetails": "It took him to such state."
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "question": "hecho",
    "questionDetails": "De hecho.",
    "answer": "fact, done",
    "answerDetails": "In fact."
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "question": "pasar",
    "questionDetails": "¿Quieres pasar el fin de semana con nosotros?",
    "answer": "spend",
    "answerDetails": "Do you want to spend the weekend with us?"
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "question": "noche",
    "questionDetails": "El jueves por la noche.",
    "answer": "night, evening",
    "answerDetails": "On Thursday night."
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "question": "igual",
    "questionDetails": "Todos nos tratamos como iguales.",
    "answer": "equal, alike, similar",
    "answerDetails": "We all treat each other as equals."
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "question": "estos",
    "questionDetails": "Glucosa se divide en dos de estos chicos.",
    "answer": "these",
    "answerDetails": "Glucose got split into two of these guys."
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "question": "cada",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy deseando ver a todos y cada uno de ustedes.",
    "answer": "each, every, such",
    "answerDetails": "I look forward to seeing each and every one of you."
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "question": "haciendo",
    "questionDetails": "Felipe logró pagar la deuda haciendo arte y vendiéndola.",
    "answer": "by making, by doing",
    "answerDetails": "Felipe was able to pay off the debt by making art and selling it."
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "question": "iba",
    "questionDetails": "¿Dónde está Leslie?-Me dijo que iba a la tienda.",
    "answer": "she was going, i was going",
    "answerDetails": "Where’s Leslie?-She told me she was going to the store."
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "question": "hombre",
    "questionDetails": "Es nuestro hombre en Moscú.",
    "answer": "man, male",
    "answerDetails": "He is our man in Moscow."
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "question": "saber",
    "questionDetails": "Saber hacer algo.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "To know how to do something."
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "question": "podemos",
    "questionDetails": "¿Estás seguro de que vamos a llegar a tiempo?-No te preocupes, podemos.",
    "answer": "we got this",
    "answerDetails": "Are you sure we’re going to make it on time?-Don’t worry, we got this."
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "question": "tienen",
    "questionDetails": "Mis padres vinieron de Guatemala a vivir conmigo en Canadá. Aunque tienen problemas para adaptarse a la cultura local, se sienten felices en su nuevo hogar.",
    "answer": "they are having",
    "answerDetails": "My parents came from Guatemala to live with me in Canada. Even though they are having problems adapting to the local culture, they feel happy in their new home."
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "question": "tú",
    "questionDetails": "Debes ir tú primero.",
    "answer": "you",
    "answerDetails": "You go out first."
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "question": "hola",
    "questionDetails": "Hola. ¿Cómo fue el vuelo?",
    "answer": "hi, hey, yo",
    "answerDetails": "‘Hi there. How was the flight?’."
  },
  {
    "id": 181,
    "question": "madre",
    "questionDetails": "La madre naturaleza.",
    "answer": "mother",
    "answerDetails": "Mother Nature."
  },
  {
    "id": 182,
    "question": "trabajo",
    "questionDetails": "Hiciste un muy buen trabajo en ese informe.",
    "answer": "job, labour, employment",
    "answerDetails": "You did a very good job with that report."
  },
  {
    "id": 183,
    "question": "fuera",
    "questionDetails": "Esperaremos fuera, para que nos puedas ver al llegar.",
    "answer": "outside, away",
    "answerDetails": "We will wait outside, so you can see us when you arrive."
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "question": "mira",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Mira! ¡ No pises el césped!.",
    "answer": "hey, take a look, she watches",
    "answerDetails": "Hey! Don’t step on the grass!."
  },
  {
    "id": 185,
    "question": "dijo",
    "questionDetails": "Le dijo al periodista que se había reunido con un agente del gobierno ruso.",
    "answer": "he told, you told, did you say",
    "answerDetails": "He told the reporter that he had met with an agent of the Russian government."
  },
  {
    "id": 186,
    "question": "digo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Por qué a ti te hace caso cuando le dices algo y a mí no?-Porque lo digo con más firmeza.",
    "answer": "i say it, i mention it",
    "answerDetails": "Why does he pay attention to you when you say something but not to me?-Because I say it more firmly."
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "question": "tus",
    "questionDetails": "Pon tus atenciones en nuestro hijo.",
    "answer": "your",
    "answerDetails": "Set your attentions towards our child."
  },
  {
    "id": 188,
    "question": "buena",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Buena!-Gracias. Mi hermano me enseñó esa jugada.",
    "answer": "nice one",
    "answerDetails": "Nice one!-Thank you. My brother taught me that play."
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "question": "seguro",
    "questionDetails": "Tuvo que revisar su diario para estar seguro del día de la semana.",
    "answer": "sure, safe, insurance",
    "answerDetails": "She had to check her diary to be sure of the day of the week."
  },
  {
    "id": 190,
    "question": "mal",
    "questionDetails": "Que estaba mal de mí.",
    "answer": "wrong, evil, poorly",
    "answerDetails": "That was wrong of me."
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "question": "ellos",
    "questionDetails": "Realmente necesito hablar con Ellos.",
    "answer": "them, they",
    "answerDetails": "I really need to talk to them."
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "question": "casi",
    "questionDetails": "Son casi las 6.",
    "answer": "almost, nearly, hardly",
    "answerDetails": "It’s almost 6 o’clock."
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "question": "entre",
    "questionDetails": "No puedes comerte los dos, tienes que elegir entre el chocolate y el Helado.",
    "answer": "between, among",
    "answerDetails": "You can’t have both, you have to choose between the chocolate bar or the ice cream."
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "question": "conmigo",
    "questionDetails": "Puedes hacer lo que quieras conmigo.",
    "answer": "me",
    "answerDetails": "You can do anything you want to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "question": "único",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos que hacer un pago único.",
    "answer": "single, only",
    "answerDetails": "We need to make a single payment."
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "question": "veo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Tuviste noticias de Marisa Últimamente?-A veces la veo caminando en el parque.",
    "answer": "i see her",
    "answerDetails": "Have you heard anything about Marisa lately?-I see her sometimes walking in the park."
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "question": "hora",
    "questionDetails": "Es hora de que nos vayamos.",
    "answer": "time, hour",
    "answerDetails": "It is time we left."
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "question": "cinco",
    "questionDetails": "El jurado tardó cinco minutos.",
    "answer": "five",
    "answerDetails": "The jury was out five minutes."
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "question": "siento",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Lo siento! No fue mi intención chocar contra ti.",
    "answer": "sorry",
    "answerDetails": "Sorry! I didn’t mean to bump you."
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "question": "dejar",
    "questionDetails": "Dejar a alguien hacer algo.",
    "answer": "leave, let, quit",
    "answerDetails": "To leave somebody to do something."
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "question": "todavía",
    "questionDetails": "¿Tu amigo todavía vive en Londres?",
    "answer": "still",
    "answerDetails": "Does your friend still live in London?"
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "question": "haber",
    "questionDetails": "Podría haberlo perdido si no lo hubieras señalado.",
    "answer": "have, be",
    "answerDetails": "I might have missed it if you hadn’t have pointed it out."
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "question": "falta",
    "questionDetails": "Demuestra cierta falta de cordura.",
    "answer": "lack, failure, absence",
    "answerDetails": "He shows a certain lack of good sense."
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "question": "hijo",
    "questionDetails": "Hijo menor/mayor.",
    "answer": "son, boy",
    "answerDetails": "Youngest/eldest son."
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "question": "ve",
    "questionDetails": "Ve a todo el mundo que entra.",
    "answer": "see",
    "answerDetails": "You see everyone who comes in."
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "question": "tampoco",
    "questionDetails": "Pero el mensaje claro no es muy claro tampoco.",
    "answer": "either, neither, nor",
    "answerDetails": "But the clear message isn’t very clear either."
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "question": "parte",
    "questionDetails": "Él era un hombre de partes-un pintor, egiptólogo, y biógrafo.",
    "answer": "part, portion, side",
    "answerDetails": "He was a man of parts—a painter, Egyptologist, and biographer."
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "question": "llegar",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuándo vamos a llegar al aeropuerto?",
    "answer": "get, arrive",
    "answerDetails": "When are we getting to the airport?"
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "question": "cuatro",
    "questionDetails": "Ya fue cuatro veces.",
    "answer": "four",
    "answerDetails": "You went four times already."
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "question": "eh",
    "questionDetails": "¿Recogiste los perros del veterinario?-¿Eh? ¡ No te oigo!.",
    "answer": "huh",
    "answerDetails": "Did you pick up the dogs from the vet?-Huh? I can’t hear you!."
  },
  {
    "id": 211,
    "question": "sabes",
    "questionDetails": "¿Qué sabes de las manifestaciones en el centro?",
    "answer": "do you know, have you heard",
    "answerDetails": "What do you know about the protests downtown?"
  },
  {
    "id": 212,
    "question": "he",
    "questionDetails": "He comido demasiado, ahora me siento mal.",
    "answer": "I have",
    "answerDetails": "I have eaten too much, now I feel sick."
  },
  {
    "id": 213,
    "question": "venir",
    "questionDetails": "Incluso podría venir aquí a estudiar.",
    "answer": "come",
    "answerDetails": "I might even come here to study."
  },
  {
    "id": 214,
    "question": "somos",
    "questionDetails": "Somos agricultores. Jamás nos mudaríamos a la ciudad.",
    "answer": "we are",
    "answerDetails": "We are farmers. We would never move to the city."
  },
  {
    "id": 215,
    "question": "ah",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Ah! Ya entendí. ¡ La tele no se enciende porque no está enchufada!.",
    "answer": "oh",
    "answerDetails": "Oh! I get it now. The TV won’t turn on because it’s not plugged in!."
  },
  {
    "id": 216,
    "question": "familia",
    "questionDetails": "La tratan como si fuera de la familia.",
    "answer": "family, children, house",
    "answerDetails": "They treat her as one of the family."
  },
  {
    "id": 217,
    "question": "esos",
    "questionDetails": "Adelante con esos discos, hombre.",
    "answer": "those",
    "answerDetails": "Come on with those records, man."
  },
  {
    "id": 218,
    "question": "hago",
    "questionDetails": "Mi mamá permite que pase toda la noche fuera con mis amigos cuando hago los quehaceres.",
    "answer": "i do",
    "answerDetails": "My mom lets me stay out all night with my friends when I do my chores."
  },
  {
    "id": 219,
    "question": "unas",
    "questionDetails": "Ahora unas palabras de nuestro patrocinador.",
    "answer": "a few",
    "answerDetails": "Now a few words from our sponsor."
  },
  {
    "id": 220,
    "question": "queda",
    "questionDetails": "Deje que nuestro progreso no enmascarar el peligro que queda.",
    "answer": "remains, stays, left",
    "answerDetails": "Let our progress there not mask the peril that remains."
  },
  {
    "id": 221,
    "question": "buen",
    "questionDetails": "Este en verdad no es un buen momento.",
    "answer": "good, nice, fine",
    "answerDetails": "This really is not a good time."
  },
  {
    "id": 222,
    "question": "además",
    "questionDetails": "Todos recibirán un aumento. Además, nos vamos todos de vacaciones.",
    "answer": "additionally, plus, further",
    "answerDetails": "Everyone is getting a raise. Additionally, we’re all going on vacation."
  },
  {
    "id": 223,
    "question": "luego",
    "questionDetails": "Ahora es mi turno, luego el tuyo.",
    "answer": "then, later, next",
    "answerDetails": "Now it’s my turn, then yours."
  },
  {
    "id": 224,
    "question": "ven",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando los alumnos ven que tomas en cuenta sus ideas, responden mejor.",
    "answer": "(they) see",
    "answerDetails": "When students see that you take their opinions into consideration, they respond better."
  },
  {
    "id": 225,
    "question": "tarde",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Buenas tardes!.",
    "answer": "afternoon, evening",
    "answerDetails": "Good afternoon!."
  },
  {
    "id": 226,
    "question": "buenas",
    "questionDetails": "Las buenas relaciones con otras culturas son primordiales para nosotros.",
    "answer": "good, nice",
    "answerDetails": "Good relations with other cultures is our highest priority."
  },
  {
    "id": 227,
    "question": "primero",
    "questionDetails": "Se ha descubierto nueva evidencia arqueológica acerca de los primeros habitantes del Perú.",
    "answer": "earliest",
    "answerDetails": "New archaeological evidence has been discovered about Peru’s earliest settlers."
  },
  {
    "id": 228,
    "question": "señor",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Oiga, señor! ¡ Se le cayó la cartera!.",
    "answer": "mister",
    "answerDetails": "Hey, mister! You dropped your wallet!."
  },
  {
    "id": 229,
    "question": "lugar",
    "questionDetails": "Intente ponerse en mi lugar.",
    "answer": "place, location, spot",
    "answerDetails": "Try to put yourself in my place."
  },
  {
    "id": 230,
    "question": "nuestro",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestro hijo mayor va a ir a la universidad el año que viene.",
    "answer": "our, what we have",
    "answerDetails": "Our eldest son is going to college next year."
  },
  {
    "id": 231,
    "question": "sabía",
    "questionDetails": "Ella sabía perfectamente bien que su madre se iba a enojar.",
    "answer": "she knew, she could",
    "answerDetails": "She knew perfectly well that her mother was going to be angry."
  },
  {
    "id": 232,
    "question": "pues",
    "questionDetails": "Pues eso es solo al principio.",
    "answer": "because",
    "answerDetails": "Because that is alone at the beginning."
  },
  {
    "id": 233,
    "question": "primera",
    "questionDetails": "Es un buen rendimiento que ordena la atención de la primera a la última.",
    "answer": "first",
    "answerDetails": "It’s a fine performance that commands attention from first to last."
  },
  {
    "id": 234,
    "question": "sobre",
    "questionDetails": "La película que vimos anoche era sobre la Primera Guerra Mundial.",
    "answer": "about, on, over",
    "answerDetails": "The movie we saw last night was about World War I."
  },
  {
    "id": 235,
    "question": "ves",
    "questionDetails": "¿Ves TV todos los días? ¿Cuántas horas por día?",
    "answer": "do you watch",
    "answerDetails": "Do you watch TV everyday? How many hours a day?"
  },
  {
    "id": 236,
    "question": "usted",
    "questionDetails": "Para usted es un hombre que puede entender.",
    "answer": "you",
    "answerDetails": "For you are a man that can understand."
  },
  {
    "id": 237,
    "question": "amor",
    "questionDetails": "No volverán por amor o dinero.",
    "answer": "love",
    "answerDetails": "They’ll not return for love or money."
  },
  {
    "id": 238,
    "question": "cualquier",
    "questionDetails": "Que tenía un trabajo de actuación por fin, y no sólo cualquier parte, pero el plomo en una nueva película.",
    "answer": "any, whatever",
    "answerDetails": "He had an acting job at last, and not just any part, but the lead in a new film."
  },
  {
    "id": 239,
    "question": "nuestra",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestra nueva casa está al lado de un bosque.",
    "answer": "our",
    "answerDetails": "Our new house is next to a forest."
  },
  {
    "id": 240,
    "question": "tienes",
    "answer": "Have"
  },
  {
    "id": 241,
    "question": "necesito",
    "questionDetails": "¿Necesito mi traje de baño para la excursión?",
    "answer": "do i need, i need him, i need to",
    "answerDetails": "Do I need my swimsuit for the outing?"
  },
  {
    "id": 242,
    "question": "allá",
    "questionDetails": "Tratando de volar en el ancho azul allá.",
    "answer": "yonder",
    "answerDetails": "Attempting to fly off into the wide blue Yonder."
  },
  {
    "id": 243,
    "question": "dios",
    "questionDetails": "La mayoría de las familias que visitamos en Bangalore tenía dioses en la casa.",
    "answer": "god",
    "answerDetails": "Most of the families we visited in Bangalore had gods in their house."
  },
  {
    "id": 244,
    "question": "importante",
    "questionDetails": "La corrupción sigue siendo un obstáculo importante para el desarrollo del País.",
    "answer": "major, significant",
    "answerDetails": "Corruption is still a major obstacle for the country’s development."
  },
  {
    "id": 245,
    "question": "ay",
    "questionDetails": "Ay, cariño; ¿te hiciste una cortadita? Déjame que te ponga una curita.",
    "answer": "aw, alas, ow",
    "answerDetails": "Aw, sweetie; did you get a booboo? Let me put a Band-aid on it."
  },
  {
    "id": 246,
    "question": "sido",
    "questionDetails": "He sido favorecido con alojamientos dentro de la villa.",
    "answer": "been",
    "answerDetails": "I have been given favoured quarters within the villa."
  },
  {
    "id": 247,
    "question": "eres",
    "questionDetails": "Así que tu eres el tipo que quiere mi vida.",
    "answer": "‘re, thou art, youre",
    "answerDetails": "So you’re the guy that wants my life."
  },
  {
    "id": 248,
    "question": "mujer",
    "questionDetails": "Había una mujer en el coche.",
    "answer": "woman",
    "answerDetails": "There was a woman in the car."
  },
  {
    "id": 249,
    "question": "venga",
    "questionDetails": "Venga, Jamie. Deja de llorar.",
    "answer": "come now, hurry up",
    "answerDetails": "Come now, Jamie. Stop crying."
  },
  {
    "id": 250,
    "question": "han",
    "questionDetails": "Y siempre han estado tan cerca.",
    "answer": "have, been, they",
    "answerDetails": "You two have always been so close."
  },
  {
    "id": 251,
    "question": "vaya",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Vaya! ¡ Qué inteligente eres!.",
    "answer": "wow, whoa",
    "answerDetails": "Wow! You’re really smart!."
  },
  {
    "id": 252,
    "question": "estas",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que estas redacciones estén acabadas para las diez.",
    "answer": "these",
    "answerDetails": "I want these compositions finished by 10."
  },
  {
    "id": 253,
    "question": "mamá",
    "questionDetails": "Todas las mamás habían ido a dejar a sus hijos en la escuela.",
    "answer": "mama, mum",
    "answerDetails": "The mamas were all dropping their kids off at school."
  },
  {
    "id": 254,
    "question": "cara",
    "questionDetails": "La cara norte del Eiger.",
    "answer": "face",
    "answerDetails": "The north face of the Eiger."
  },
  {
    "id": 255,
    "question": "lado",
    "questionDetails": "Permanece a mi lado por siempre.",
    "answer": "side",
    "answerDetails": "Be by my side forever."
  },
  {
    "id": 256,
    "question": "cabeza",
    "questionDetails": "En casa puedo bajar la cabeza y continuar con el trabajo en la mano.",
    "answer": "head, neck, mind",
    "answerDetails": "At home I can get my head down and get on with the job in hand."
  },
  {
    "id": 257,
    "question": "llama",
    "questionDetails": "Sus palabras avivaron en él la llama de la venganza.",
    "answer": "flame",
    "answerDetails": "Her words kindled the flame of revenge in him."
  },
  {
    "id": 258,
    "question": "quieres",
    "questionDetails": "Lo que quieres está fuera de tu alcance.",
    "answer": "you want",
    "answerDetails": "What you want is out of your reach."
  },
  {
    "id": 259,
    "question": "padre",
    "questionDetails": "Varios de los padres de la aldea fueron al pueblo vecino para asistir a una junta.",
    "answer": "father, parent",
    "answerDetails": "Several of the town fathers went to the next town to attend a meeting."
  },
  {
    "id": 260,
    "question": "mano",
    "questionDetails": "Las cosas se estaban poniendo un poco de la mano en la línea de piquete.",
    "answer": "hand, palm",
    "answerDetails": "Things were getting a bit out of hand at the picket line."
  },
  {
    "id": 261,
    "question": "papá",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Mi papá es el hombre más fuerte del mundo!.",
    "answer": "dad",
    "answerDetails": "My dad is the strongest man in the world!."
  },
  {
    "id": 262,
    "question": "perdón",
    "questionDetails": "¿Perdón? ¿Puedes repetir lo que dijiste?",
    "answer": "pardon",
    "answerDetails": "Pardon? Could you repeat what you said?"
  },
  {
    "id": 263,
    "question": "problema",
    "questionDetails": "El problema del edadismo en Hollywood.",
    "answer": "problem, issue",
    "answerDetails": "The problem of ageism in Hollywood."
  },
  {
    "id": 264,
    "question": "poder",
    "questionDetails": "El poder está en manos de los consumidores.",
    "answer": "power",
    "answerDetails": "The power is in the hands of the consumers."
  },
  {
    "id": 265,
    "question": "pasado",
    "questionDetails": "Le pareció difícil llegar a fin de cumplir en el pasado.",
    "answer": "past, last",
    "answerDetails": "She found it hard to make ends meet in the past."
  },
  {
    "id": 266,
    "question": "cuidado",
    "questionDetails": "Política que aboga que el cuidado de discapacitados o ancianos no dependa de instituciones como hospitales o asilos, sino de sus familias y la comunidad en general.",
    "answer": "care, caution",
    "answerDetails": "Care in the community."
  },
  {
    "id": 267,
    "question": "dicen",
    "questionDetails": "No los entiendo, dicen algo raro.",
    "answer": "say, tell, claim",
    "answerDetails": "I do not understand, say something funny."
  },
  {
    "id": 268,
    "question": "ti",
    "answer": "thee"
  },
  {
    "id": 269,
    "question": "ustedes",
    "questionDetails": "No lograrán nada si no hacen más que pelearse entre ustedes.",
    "answer": "yourselves",
    "answerDetails": "You’ll never achieve anything if all you do is fight among yourselves."
  },
  {
    "id": 270,
    "question": "volver",
    "questionDetails": "Se levantó una tormenta y el barco tuvo que volver a Puerto.",
    "answer": "turn back, revert",
    "answerDetails": "A storm blew up and the boat had to turn back to port."
  },
  {
    "id": 271,
    "question": "mucha",
    "questionDetails": "No tiene mucha imaginación para los alias.",
    "answer": "much",
    "answerDetails": "Not much imagination for an alias."
  },
  {
    "id": 272,
    "question": "nombre",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca dices bien mi nombre.",
    "answer": "name",
    "answerDetails": "You never get my name right."
  },
  {
    "id": 273,
    "question": "nuevo",
    "questionDetails": "El Museo está cerrado al público hasta nuevo aviso.",
    "answer": "further, fresh",
    "answerDetails": "The museum is closed to the public until further notice."
  },
  {
    "id": 274,
    "question": "idea",
    "questionDetails": "Acabo de tener una idea. ¡ Vayámonos de vacaciones!.",
    "answer": "thought, notion, concept",
    "answerDetails": "I just had a thought. Let’s go on vacation!."
  },
  {
    "id": 275,
    "question": "caso",
    "questionDetails": "El número de casos de cáncer está aumentando.",
    "answer": "case, instance",
    "answerDetails": "The number of cancer cases is increasing."
  },
  {
    "id": 276,
    "question": "visto",
    "answer": "since"
  },
  {
    "id": 277,
    "question": "algún",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo algún coctel listo.",
    "answer": "some",
    "answerDetails": "I have some cocktails ready."
  },
  {
    "id": 278,
    "question": "horas",
    "questionDetails": "Dijo que casi había terminado el vestido, pero lleva horas diciendo lo mismo.",
    "answer": "hours",
    "answerDetails": "She said she’s nearly finished making the dress, but she’s been saying that for Hours."
  },
  {
    "id": 279,
    "question": "esas",
    "questionDetails": "Esas no son las cajas que te pedí.",
    "answer": "those",
    "answerDetails": "Those aren’t the boxes I asked you for."
  },
  {
    "id": 280,
    "question": "estado",
    "questionDetails": "La ruptura la puso en un estado terrible de depresión.",
    "answer": "state, status, condition",
    "answerDetails": "The breakup put her in a terrible state of depression."
  },
  {
    "id": 281,
    "question": "tomar",
    "questionDetails": "Tomarlo de mí, Kid-he estado allí, hecho, visto todo.",
    "answer": "take",
    "answerDetails": "Take it from me, kid—I’ve been there, done it, seen it all."
  },
  {
    "id": 282,
    "question": "cuál",
    "questionDetails": "Cuestiona cuál es el paradigma de este texto.",
    "answer": "what",
    "answerDetails": "He questioned what the paradigm in this novel was."
  },
  {
    "id": 283,
    "question": "cuánto",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que sepas cuánto significa para mí.",
    "answer": "how much, how",
    "answerDetails": "I hope you know how much you mean to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 284,
    "question": "hablando",
    "questionDetails": "Estás hablando con un trébol.",
    "answer": "talking, speaking, talkin’",
    "answerDetails": "Are you talking to what clover."
  },
  {
    "id": 285,
    "question": "miedo",
    "questionDetails": "Me se encogió en el miedo como balas silbó pasado.",
    "answer": "fear, fright",
    "answerDetails": "I cowered in fear as bullets whizzed past."
  },
  {
    "id": 286,
    "question": "vi",
    "questionDetails": "Jason pareció estar un poco triste cuando lo vi hoy.",
    "answer": "i saw him, i saw that",
    "answerDetails": "Jason seemed a little sad when I saw him today."
  },
  {
    "id": 287,
    "question": "alguna",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo muchas manzanas. ¿Quieres alguna?",
    "answer": "any, some",
    "answerDetails": "I have lots of apples. Do you want any?"
  },
  {
    "id": 288,
    "question": "hizo",
    "questionDetails": "Mi hijo dijo que lavaría los platos, y después que terminó sus tareas lo hizo.",
    "answer": "he did, it made it, it did it",
    "answerDetails": "My son said he would wash the dishes, and after he finished his homework he did."
  },
  {
    "id": 289,
    "question": "dicho",
    "questionDetails": "Mi abuela siempre estaba soltando viejos dichos.",
    "answer": "saying",
    "answerDetails": "My grandmother was always spouting old sayings."
  },
  {
    "id": 290,
    "question": "acuerdo",
    "questionDetails": "El Comité llegó a un acuerdo en cuanto al horario del club.",
    "answer": "agreement, settlement, arrangement",
    "answerDetails": "The committee reached an agreement regarding the club hours."
  },
  {
    "id": 291,
    "question": "aunque",
    "questionDetails": "Aunque pequeña, la habitación tiene una sensación espaciosa.",
    "answer": "although, while",
    "answerDetails": "Although small, the room has a spacious feel."
  },
  {
    "id": 292,
    "question": "hacemos",
    "questionDetails": "¿Dónde imprimen sus fotografías?-Las hacemos nosotros en casa.",
    "answer": "we do them",
    "answerDetails": "Where do you get your photos printed?-We do them ourselves at home."
  },
  {
    "id": 293,
    "question": "grande",
    "questionDetails": "Compramos madera en grandes cantidades.",
    "answer": "large, big, spacious",
    "answerDetails": "We bought timber in large quantities."
  },
  {
    "id": 294,
    "question": "puedes",
    "questionDetails": "Todo lo que puedes hacer es estar allí para él.",
    "answer": "can",
    "answerDetails": "All you can do is be there for them."
  },
  {
    "id": 295,
    "question": "razón",
    "questionDetails": "La gente está dispuesta, dentro de la razón, a pagar la escolarización.",
    "answer": "reason",
    "answerDetails": "People are willing, within reason, to pay for schooling."
  },
  {
    "id": 296,
    "question": "mío",
    "questionDetails": "El vuestro parece más elevado que el mío.",
    "answer": "mine",
    "answerDetails": "Yours seems to be higher than mine."
  },
  {
    "id": 297,
    "question": "cuándo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Hasta cuándo te puedes quedar?",
    "answer": "when",
    "answerDetails": "Until when can you stay?"
  },
  {
    "id": 298,
    "question": "buenos",
    "questionDetails": "Tus chicos son demasiado buenos para mí.",
    "answer": "good, nice",
    "answerDetails": "You guys are too good to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 299,
    "question": "importa",
    "answer": "Matter"
  },
  {
    "id": 300,
    "question": "amigo",
    "questionDetails": "Hacerse amigo de alguien.",
    "answer": "friend, dude",
    "answerDetails": "To make friends with somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 301,
    "question": "ningún",
    "questionDetails": "No quiero ningún problema para mi gente.",
    "answer": "any",
    "answerDetails": "I want not any trouble for my people."
  },
  {
    "id": 302,
    "question": "pueden",
    "questionDetails": "Así que como pueden ver, es una linda máquina.",
    "answer": "can, may",
    "answerDetails": "So as you can see, really nice machine."
  },
  {
    "id": 303,
    "question": "deja",
    "answer": "it allows"
  },
  {
    "id": 304,
    "question": "amigos",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero mi propia casa, mis propios amigos.",
    "answer": "friends",
    "answerDetails": "I want my own friends."
  },
  {
    "id": 305,
    "question": "serio",
    "questionDetails": "No lo decía en serio.",
    "answer": "serious, earnest",
    "answerDetails": "It wasn’t a serious suggestion."
  },
  {
    "id": 306,
    "question": "haces",
    "questionDetails": "Tú siempre haces lo correcto.",
    "answer": "do, beams, bundles",
    "answerDetails": "You always do what is right."
  },
  {
    "id": 307,
    "question": "puerta",
    "questionDetails": "Caminó a través de la puerta.",
    "answer": "door, gate",
    "answerDetails": "She walked through the door."
  },
  {
    "id": 308,
    "question": "hacen",
    "questionDetails": "Todo lo que hacen, lo hacen con mucha energía.",
    "answer": "they do it, they make it",
    "answerDetails": "Everything they do, they do it with a lot of energy."
  },
  {
    "id": 309,
    "question": "persona",
    "questionDetails": "Una empresa legalmente constituida es una persona jurídica.",
    "answer": "entity",
    "answerDetails": "A lawfully established enterprise is a legal entity."
  },
  {
    "id": 310,
    "question": "poner",
    "questionDetails": "Las normas que vamos a poner en marcha en los próximos meses cumplen estos criterios.",
    "answer": "place",
    "answerDetails": "The rules which we shall put in place in the months ahead meet these criteria."
  },
  {
    "id": 311,
    "question": "fui",
    "questionDetails": "Me fui a cenar.",
    "answer": "went, left",
    "answerDetails": "I went to dinner."
  },
  {
    "id": 312,
    "question": "vivir",
    "questionDetails": "Vivir una vida feliz/larga.",
    "answer": "live",
    "answerDetails": "To live a happy/long life."
  },
  {
    "id": 313,
    "question": "fin",
    "questionDetails": "Si invaden, no habrá fin.",
    "answer": "end, order, purpose",
    "answerDetails": "If you invade, there’ll be no end."
  },
  {
    "id": 314,
    "question": "arriba",
    "questionDetails": "Había varios arqueros apuntándonos desde arriba.",
    "answer": "above, upstairs, overhead",
    "answerDetails": "There were several archers aiming at us from above."
  },
  {
    "id": 315,
    "question": "año",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo 10 años y mi hermano tiene cinco.",
    "answer": "year",
    "answerDetails": "I am 10 years old and my brother is five."
  },
  {
    "id": 316,
    "question": "entiendo",
    "questionDetails": "La novela me resultó muy confusa.-Yo la entiendo bastante bien.",
    "answer": "i understand, i know it, i see that",
    "answerDetails": "The novel was very confusing to me.-I understand it pretty well."
  },
  {
    "id": 317,
    "question": "pensar",
    "questionDetails": "Fui a caminar para tener un pensar.",
    "answer": "think",
    "answerDetails": "I went for a walk to have a think."
  },
  {
    "id": 318,
    "question": "gran",
    "questionDetails": "Si el alto el fuego continúa, será un gran alivio para todos nosotros.",
    "answer": "great, grand, high",
    "answerDetails": "If this ceasefire holds, it would be a great relief for us all."
  },
  {
    "id": 319,
    "question": "hice",
    "answer": "Did"
  },
  {
    "id": 320,
    "question": "quieren",
    "questionDetails": "No subestimen a sus padres. Los quieren tanto.",
    "answer": "they love you, you all want",
    "answerDetails": "Don’t take your parents for granted. They love you so much."
  },
  {
    "id": 321,
    "question": "muchos",
    "questionDetails": "Hemos sido amigos por muchos años.",
    "answer": "many",
    "answerDetails": "We have been friends for many years."
  },
  {
    "id": 322,
    "question": "vale",
    "questionDetails": "La compañía me dará un vale de viaje para el viaje de negocios.",
    "answer": "voucher, okay, it is worth",
    "answerDetails": "The company is going to give me a travel voucher for the business trip."
  },
  {
    "id": 323,
    "question": "será",
    "questionDetails": "Roxanne es una muy buena cantante y sé que será famosa algún día.",
    "answer": "she will be, it will be",
    "answerDetails": "Roxanne is such a good singer that I know she will be famous some Day."
  },
  {
    "id": 324,
    "question": "tipo",
    "questionDetails": "Había todo tipo de libros en la biblioteca.",
    "answer": "kind, guy, figure",
    "answerDetails": "There were all kinds of books at the library."
  },
  {
    "id": 325,
    "question": "debe",
    "questionDetails": "El jefe de Peter Le dijo que debe estar en la oficina a las 7.",
    "answer": "he must, she should",
    "answerDetails": "Peter’s boss told him that he must be in the office at 7."
  },
  {
    "id": 326,
    "question": "has",
    "questionDetails": "¿Has visto esta película?",
    "answer": "have you",
    "answerDetails": "Have you seen this movie before?"
  },
  {
    "id": 327,
    "question": "seguir",
    "questionDetails": "Sigo sin seguirte.",
    "answer": "follow, continue, keep",
    "answerDetails": "I still don’t follow you."
  },
  {
    "id": 328,
    "question": "dio",
    "questionDetails": "Me dio tu libro y me pidió que te lo diera.",
    "answer": "he gave, it gave, he offered",
    "answerDetails": "He gave me your book and asked me to give it to you."
  },
  {
    "id": 329,
    "question": "difícil",
    "questionDetails": "Tuvo una difícil decisión de hacer.",
    "answer": "difficult",
    "answerDetails": "She had a difficult decision to make."
  },
  {
    "id": 330,
    "question": "vino",
    "questionDetails": "Carta de vinos.",
    "answer": "wine",
    "answerDetails": "Wine list."
  },
  {
    "id": 331,
    "question": "agua",
    "questionDetails": "La calzada estaba bajo el agua.",
    "answer": "water",
    "answerDetails": "The Causeway was under water."
  },
  {
    "id": 332,
    "question": "espera",
    "questionDetails": "Los bomberos están en espera en el espectáculo de fuegos pirotécnicos.",
    "answer": "standby",
    "answerDetails": "Firefighters are on standby at the fireworks show."
  },
  {
    "id": 333,
    "question": "final",
    "questionDetails": "El café está al final de la calle a la derecha.",
    "answer": "end, finish, ultimate",
    "answerDetails": "The coffee shop is at the end of the street on the right."
  },
  {
    "id": 334,
    "question": "toma",
    "questionDetails": "El cuarto juego fue de Wright para la toma de.",
    "answer": "taking, shot, jack",
    "answerDetails": "The fourth game was Wright’s for the taking."
  },
  {
    "id": 335,
    "question": "diez",
    "questionDetails": "Diez artículos o menos.",
    "answer": "ten",
    "answerDetails": "Ten item or less."
  },
  {
    "id": 336,
    "question": "contigo",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero ir al cine contigo.",
    "answer": "with you, on you",
    "answerDetails": "I want to go with you to the movies."
  },
  {
    "id": 337,
    "question": "dinero",
    "questionDetails": "Aceptó el trabajo en el Banco ya que el dinero era mejor.",
    "answer": "money",
    "answerDetails": "She accepted the job at the bank since the money was better."
  },
  {
    "id": 338,
    "question": "quedar",
    "questionDetails": "Ahora te puedes quedar.",
    "answer": "stay",
    "answerDetails": "Now you can stay."
  },
  {
    "id": 339,
    "question": "medio",
    "questionDetails": "Medio ambiente.",
    "answer": "environment, middle, medium",
    "answerDetails": "Environment."
  },
  {
    "id": 340,
    "question": "acá",
    "questionDetails": "El insistió, por eso estamos acá.",
    "answer": "here, hither",
    "answerDetails": "He insisted, so here we are."
  },
  {
    "id": 341,
    "question": "manera",
    "questionDetails": "Prefiero hacer las cosas a mi manera.",
    "answer": "way, manner, fashion",
    "answerDetails": "I prefer doing things my way."
  },
  {
    "id": 342,
    "question": "hubiera",
    "questionDetails": "Si hubiera entre los presentes alguien que se oponga a esta Unión, que hable ahora o calle para siempre.",
    "answer": "there be",
    "answerDetails": "If there be anyone among us who objects to this union, let him speak now or forever hold his peace."
  },
  {
    "id": 343,
    "question": "hemos",
    "questionDetails": "Hemos entrado en una nueva era.",
    "answer": "we",
    "answerDetails": "We are in a new era."
  },
  {
    "id": 344,
    "question": "llevo",
    "questionDetails": "Le llevo a su hijo cada dos semanas.",
    "answer": "take, carry",
    "answerDetails": "I take her child to her every two weeks."
  },
  {
    "id": 345,
    "question": "haga",
    "questionDetails": "No me haga usted la alimentación forzada.",
    "answer": "make, do",
    "answerDetails": "Do not make me feed you forced."
  },
  {
    "id": 346,
    "question": "poquito",
    "questionDetails": "Algo un poquito mas estricto.",
    "answer": "little",
    "answerDetails": "Something a little more stringent."
  },
  {
    "id": 347,
    "question": "adelante",
    "questionDetails": "Mirando hacia adelante, se espera que las ganancias golpeen £ 7, 2000 millones.",
    "answer": "forward, further, go on",
    "answerDetails": "Looking forward, earnings are expected to hit £7.2 billion."
  },
  {
    "id": 348,
    "question": "buscar",
    "questionDetails": "Buscaron por todas partes el cachorro que se les había perdido.",
    "answer": "search, pursue",
    "answerDetails": "They searched everywhere for their lost puppy."
  },
  {
    "id": 349,
    "question": "podía",
    "questionDetails": "Podía nadar millas a la vez antes del accidente.",
    "answer": "he was able, it could, he could",
    "answerDetails": "He was able to swim for miles at a time before his accident."
  },
  {
    "id": 350,
    "question": "juntos",
    "questionDetails": "Ir juntos (AS).",
    "answer": "together",
    "answerDetails": "To go or belong together."
  },
  {
    "id": 351,
    "question": "fácil",
    "questionDetails": "Su reputación en la escuela por ser fácil.",
    "answer": "easy",
    "answerDetails": "Her reputation at school for being easy."
  },
  {
    "id": 352,
    "question": "eran",
    "questionDetails": "Los peregrinos partieron para el Nuevo Mundo porque eran marginados donde vivían.",
    "answer": "they were",
    "answerDetails": "The pilgrims left for the New World because they were outcasts where they were living."
  },
  {
    "id": 353,
    "question": "oye",
    "questionDetails": "Oye, ¿qué está pasando aquí?",
    "answer": "hey, yo",
    "answerDetails": "Hey, what’s going on here?"
  },
  {
    "id": 354,
    "question": "sigue",
    "questionDetails": "El camino gira hacia el este. Sigue el curso del río.",
    "answer": "it follows, keep going, drive on",
    "answerDetails": "The road turns to the east. It follows the course of the river."
  },
  {
    "id": 355,
    "question": "sería",
    "questionDetails": "Ud. sería presidente ahora si no hubiera sido por ese escándalo.",
    "answer": "you would be, he would be, it would be",
    "answerDetails": "You would be president by now if it hadn’t been for that scandal."
  },
  {
    "id": 356,
    "question": "comer",
    "questionDetails": "Él los comería fuera de casa y en casa si continuaba corriendo a través de galletas a su ritmo actual.",
    "answer": "eat",
    "answerDetails": "He would eat them out of house and home if he continued to run through biscuits at his present rate."
  },
  {
    "id": 357,
    "question": "suerte",
    "questionDetails": "Estar de suerte.",
    "answer": "luck, fortune",
    "answerDetails": "To be in luck."
  },
  {
    "id": 358,
    "question": "tranquilo",
    "questionDetails": "Su estado de ánimo tranquilo desapareció.",
    "answer": "peaceful, calm, relaxed",
    "answerDetails": "His peaceful mood vanished."
  },
  {
    "id": 359,
    "question": "manos",
    "questionDetails": "La posesión de Alsacia ha cambiado de manos muchas veces a lo largo de la historia.",
    "answer": "hands",
    "answerDetails": "Possession of Alsace has changed hands many times over the course of history."
  },
  {
    "id": 360,
    "question": "señora",
    "questionDetails": "Hablé con una señora mayor en la biblioteca.",
    "answer": "lady, missus",
    "answerDetails": "I talked to an old lady at the library."
  },
  {
    "id": 361,
    "question": "cierto",
    "questionDetails": "Que no es cierto de la gente de la que hablo.",
    "answer": "true",
    "answerDetails": "That is not true of the people I am talking about."
  },
  {
    "id": 362,
    "question": "sola",
    "questionDetails": "Nadie quiso ayudarle a Jane con su tarea, así que la hizo sola.",
    "answer": "on her own",
    "answerDetails": "Nobody wanted to help Jane with her homework, so she did it on her own."
  },
  {
    "id": 363,
    "question": "llevar",
    "questionDetails": "Él era la única persona que podía llevar el país a través de.",
    "answer": "carry, bring, conduct",
    "answerDetails": "He was the only person who could carry the country through."
  },
  {
    "id": 364,
    "question": "paso",
    "questionDetails": "Muchas oscilaciones rastrear el mismo patrón, pero necesariamente en el paso.",
    "answer": "step, passage, way",
    "answerDetails": "Many oscillations trace out the same pattern but necessarily in step."
  },
  {
    "id": 365,
    "question": "dentro",
    "questionDetails": "Jackson te está esperando dentro.",
    "answer": "inside",
    "answerDetails": "Mr Jackson is waiting for you inside."
  },
  {
    "id": 366,
    "question": "pensé",
    "questionDetails": "Pensé y pensé pero no pude dar con la respuesta.",
    "answer": "i thought",
    "answerDetails": "I thought and thought, but I couldn’t come up with the answer."
  },
  {
    "id": 367,
    "question": "rápido",
    "questionDetails": "Fue rápido de él para detectar el error.",
    "answer": "quick, rapid, prompt",
    "answerDetails": "It was quick of him to spot the mistake."
  },
  {
    "id": 368,
    "question": "vemos",
    "questionDetails": "A veces los vemos andando hacia la parada de autobús cuando vamos a llevar los niños a la escuela.",
    "answer": "we see you",
    "answerDetails": "Sometimes we see you walking to the bus stop when we’re taking the children to school."
  },
  {
    "id": 369,
    "question": "entrar",
    "questionDetails": "Ganaron cada carrera que entraron.",
    "answer": "enter",
    "answerDetails": "They won every race they entered."
  },
  {
    "id": 370,
    "question": "podría",
    "questionDetails": "Podría ser mejor esperar a que llegue.",
    "answer": "it could, he could",
    "answerDetails": "It could be better to wait until he arrives."
  },
  {
    "id": 371,
    "question": "crees",
    "questionDetails": "¿Crees en los fantasmas?-No, no creo en ellos. Soy demasiado racional.",
    "answer": "do you believe",
    "answerDetails": "Do you believe in ghosts?-No, I don’t. I’m too rational."
  },
  {
    "id": 372,
    "question": "trabajar",
    "questionDetails": "Trabajar para alguien.",
    "answer": "work, put in",
    "answerDetails": "To work for somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 373,
    "question": "última",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Vaya! ¡ La última de tu primo es increíble!.",
    "answer": "latest",
    "answerDetails": "Well, your cousin’s latest is unbelievable!."
  },
  {
    "id": 374,
    "question": "minutos",
    "questionDetails": "El jurado tardó cinco minutos.",
    "answer": "minutes, mins, min",
    "answerDetails": "The jury was out five minutes."
  },
  {
    "id": 375,
    "question": "semana",
    "questionDetails": "Trabajo durante la semana, así que sólo puedo llegar a esta tienda los sábados.",
    "answer": "week",
    "answerDetails": "I work during the week, so I can only get to this shop on Saturdays."
  },
  {
    "id": 376,
    "question": "hija",
    "questionDetails": "Va a casar a su hija, en este lugar.",
    "answer": "daughter",
    "answerDetails": "She will marry her daughter here, in her stead."
  },
  {
    "id": 377,
    "question": "vengo",
    "questionDetails": "Vengo siempre que me llamas.",
    "answer": "i come, i am coming",
    "answerDetails": "I come whenever you call me."
  },
  {
    "id": 378,
    "question": "sale",
    "questionDetails": "Él sale al mediodía. Mi vuelo, en cambio, sale a las 3 pm.",
    "answer": "he leaves, he comes out, he gets out",
    "answerDetails": "He leaves at noon. My flight, on the other hand, departs at 3 P.M."
  },
  {
    "id": 379,
    "question": "atrás",
    "questionDetails": "Ella salió de la habitación sin una mirada hacia atrás.",
    "answer": "backward",
    "answerDetails": "She left the room without a backward glance."
  },
  {
    "id": 380,
    "question": "seis",
    "questionDetails": "Y entonces quedamos seis.",
    "answer": "six",
    "answerDetails": "And then there were six."
  },
  {
    "id": 381,
    "question": "pasando",
    "questionDetails": "La gente debe saber lo que esta pasando.",
    "answer": "happening, passing, going",
    "answerDetails": "The people must be told what is happening."
  },
  {
    "id": 382,
    "question": "hijos",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo 4 hijos: Ana, Marta, Antonio y Miguel.",
    "answer": "children, sons, kids",
    "answerDetails": "I have four children: Ana, Marta, Antonio, and Miguel."
  },
  {
    "id": 383,
    "question": "habla",
    "questionDetails": "Parece que los abogados tienen su propia habla.",
    "answer": "language, she talks",
    "answerDetails": "Lawyers seem to have their own language."
  },
  {
    "id": 384,
    "question": "mientras",
    "questionDetails": "Nada cambió mucho mientras estaba ausente.",
    "answer": "while, whereas, whilst",
    "answerDetails": "Nothing much changed while he was away."
  },
  {
    "id": 385,
    "question": "punto",
    "questionDetails": "Hasta cierto punto.",
    "answer": "point, spot, item",
    "answerDetails": "Up to a point."
  },
  {
    "id": 386,
    "question": "fuerte",
    "questionDetails": "La competencia era demasiado fuerte.",
    "answer": "strong, high, heavy",
    "answerDetails": "The competition was too strong."
  },
  {
    "id": 387,
    "question": "segundo",
    "questionDetails": "El segundo del boxeador intentó cerrar la herida después de una ronda brutal.",
    "answer": "second",
    "answerDetails": "The boxer’s second tried to close the cut after a brutal round."
  },
  {
    "id": 388,
    "question": "dale",
    "questionDetails": "Dale tiempo para pensar. Es una decisión importante.",
    "answer": "give her, get him, get it",
    "answerDetails": "Give her time to think. It’s an important decision."
  },
  {
    "id": 389,
    "question": "ayudar",
    "questionDetails": "Ayudar a alguien a ponerse/quitarse or.",
    "answer": "help, assist",
    "answerDetails": "To help somebody on/off with his coat."
  },
  {
    "id": 390,
    "question": "ninguna",
    "questionDetails": "No hay ninguna manera de que ella vaya al baile conmigo.",
    "answer": "no, any",
    "answerDetails": "There is no way she will go to the dance with me."
  },
  {
    "id": 391,
    "question": "misma",
    "questionDetails": "Se te cobró por el transporte de la mercancía y la entrega de la misma.",
    "answer": "same",
    "answerDetails": "You were charged for the transport of the merchandise and delivery of same."
  },
  {
    "id": 392,
    "question": "dormir",
    "questionDetails": "Tomaron su Pit Bull Terrier en un viaje a Francia antes de que se pusiera a dormir.",
    "answer": "sleep",
    "answerDetails": "They took their pit bull terrier on a trip to France before having her put to sleep."
  },
  {
    "id": 393,
    "question": "historia",
    "questionDetails": "La historia del Imperio.",
    "answer": "history",
    "answerDetails": "The history of the Empire."
  },
  {
    "id": 394,
    "question": "diga",
    "questionDetails": "Diga.-Hola. ¿Se encuentra María?",
    "answer": "hello",
    "answerDetails": "Hello.-Hi. Is Maria there?"
  },
  {
    "id": 395,
    "question": "llegó",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando llegó a la casa, todos gritaron, “¡ Sorpresa!”.",
    "answer": "she came, he made it",
    "answerDetails": "When she came to the house, everybody yelled, “surprise!”."
  },
  {
    "id": 396,
    "question": "tenido",
    "answer": "tinted"
  },
  {
    "id": 397,
    "question": "esperando",
    "questionDetails": "Me aburro esperando en la fila.",
    "answer": "while waiting",
    "answerDetails": "I get bored while waiting in line."
  },
  {
    "id": 398,
    "question": "dame",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Dame mi muñeca ya o le voy a decir a mami!.",
    "answer": "gimme",
    "answerDetails": "Gimme my doll now or I’ll tell mommy!."
  },
  {
    "id": 399,
    "question": "tenga",
    "questionDetails": "Sr., quiero que tenga esta cobija. Tenga. Y feliz Navidad.",
    "answer": "here you are",
    "answerDetails": "Sir, I want you to have this blanket. Here you are. Have a merry Christmas."
  },
  {
    "id": 400,
    "question": "encontrar",
    "answer": "to be"
  },
  {
    "id": 401,
    "question": "gusto",
    "questionDetails": "Las aves no tienen un sentido del gusto muy desarrollado.",
    "answer": "taste, pleasure, flavor",
    "answerDetails": "Birds do not have a highly developed sense of taste."
  },
  {
    "id": 402,
    "question": "haya",
    "questionDetails": "Base de madera de haya laminada y curvada.",
    "answer": "beech",
    "answerDetails": "Base in laminated and curved beech."
  },
  {
    "id": 403,
    "question": "buscando",
    "answer": "in search of"
  },
  {
    "id": 404,
    "question": "peor",
    "questionDetails": "(Él) llevó la peor parte, él fue quien salió peor.",
    "answer": "worst, worse",
    "answerDetails": "He came off worst."
  },
  {
    "id": 405,
    "question": "meses",
    "questionDetails": "Hemos trabajado en el túnel de viento por meses.",
    "answer": "months",
    "answerDetails": "You have the wind tunnel for months."
  },
  {
    "id": 406,
    "question": "hermano",
    "questionDetails": "El hermano Rafael es el director de la abadía.",
    "answer": "brother",
    "answerDetails": "Brother Rafael is the abbey’s director."
  },
  {
    "id": 407,
    "question": "problemas",
    "questionDetails": "Ella estaba demasiado preocupado con sus propios sentimientos a los problemas de Clare.",
    "answer": "trouble",
    "answerDetails": "She was too concerned with her own feelings to trouble about Clare’s."
  },
  {
    "id": 408,
    "question": "quien",
    "questionDetails": "Puede que sólo sepas quien lo hizo.",
    "answer": "who, whom",
    "answerDetails": "Maybe just you know who did it."
  },
  {
    "id": 409,
    "question": "corazón",
    "questionDetails": "Claro que es un corazón real.",
    "answer": "heart",
    "answerDetails": "Of course it was a real heart."
  },
  {
    "id": 410,
    "question": "anda",
    "answer": "well"
  },
  {
    "id": 411,
    "question": "ayuda",
    "questionDetails": "Caminó con la ayuda de un marco de Zimmer.",
    "answer": "aid, support, assistance",
    "answerDetails": "She walked with the aid of a Zimmer frame."
  },
  {
    "id": 412,
    "question": "lleva",
    "questionDetails": "Ella solo lleva ropa negra porque está de luto.",
    "answer": "she wears, she brings, he carries",
    "answerDetails": "She wears only black because she’s in mourning."
  },
  {
    "id": 413,
    "question": "primer",
    "questionDetails": "Ella está en sus primeros años 50.",
    "answer": "early",
    "answerDetails": "She’s in her early fifties."
  },
  {
    "id": 414,
    "question": "contra",
    "questionDetails": "Nadar contra corriente del río exige mucho esfuerzo.",
    "answer": "against, on",
    "answerDetails": "Swimming against the current of the river takes much effort."
  },
  {
    "id": 415,
    "question": "conozco",
    "questionDetails": "¿Quiénes son esos muchachos?-Oh, yo los conozco. Son mis vecinos.",
    "answer": "i know them",
    "answerDetails": "Who are those boys over there?-Oh, I know them. They’re my neighbors."
  },
  {
    "id": 416,
    "question": "diciendo",
    "questionDetails": "La directora abrió la rueda de prensa diciendo que estaba encantada con el galardón.",
    "answer": "by saying",
    "answerDetails": "The director opened the press conference by saying she was delighted with the award."
  },
  {
    "id": 417,
    "question": "dices",
    "questionDetails": "Lo que dices no tiene sentido.",
    "answer": "say, tell",
    "answerDetails": "What you say doesn’t make sense."
  },
  {
    "id": 418,
    "question": "encima",
    "questionDetails": "El espejo está encima de la silla.",
    "answer": "above, on me",
    "answerDetails": "The mirror is above the chair."
  },
  {
    "id": 419,
    "question": "di",
    "questionDetails": "Mamá, ¿viste mis llaves?-¡ Te las di hace 2 minutos!.",
    "answer": "i gave",
    "answerDetails": "Mom, did you see my keys?-I gave them to you two minutes ago!."
  },
  {
    "id": 420,
    "question": "das",
    "questionDetails": "Solamente si me das una buena razón.",
    "answer": "give",
    "answerDetails": "If you give me a good reason."
  },
  {
    "id": 421,
    "question": "tranquila",
    "questionDetails": "Era una tranquila velada en casa.",
    "answer": "quiet, calm, peaceful",
    "answerDetails": "Just having a quiet evening at home."
  },
  {
    "id": 422,
    "question": "mía",
    "questionDetails": "No es mía, no se la puedo dar.",
    "answer": "mine",
    "answerDetails": "She is not mine to give."
  },
  {
    "id": 423,
    "question": "nueva",
    "questionDetails": "Hemos entrado en una nueva era.",
    "answer": "new",
    "answerDetails": "We are in a new era."
  },
  {
    "id": 424,
    "question": "cambiar",
    "questionDetails": "Necesitamos cambiar las opiniones de la gente si vamos a ganar esta campaña.",
    "answer": "shift",
    "answerDetails": "We need to shift people’s opinions if we are going to win this campaign."
  },
  {
    "id": 425,
    "question": "listo",
    "questionDetails": "El asesino sabía que el mazo estaría listo para la mano.",
    "answer": "ready, done, smart",
    "answerDetails": "The murderer knew that the Mallet would be ready to hand."
  },
  {
    "id": 426,
    "question": "feliz",
    "questionDetails": "Tenía la destreza feliz de hacer que la gente como él.",
    "answer": "happy, merry",
    "answerDetails": "He had the happy knack of making people like him."
  },
  {
    "id": 427,
    "question": "tuve",
    "questionDetails": "Le tuve que invitar.",
    "answer": "had",
    "answerDetails": "I had to invite him."
  },
  {
    "id": 428,
    "question": "perfecto",
    "questionDetails": "496 es un número perfecto.",
    "answer": "perfect",
    "answerDetails": "496 is a perfect number."
  },
  {
    "id": 429,
    "question": "ojos",
    "questionDetails": "El pelo de Casey está muy largo y no se le ven los ojos.",
    "answer": "her eyes, his eyes",
    "answerDetails": "Casey’s hair is too long, and you can’t see her eyes."
  },
  {
    "id": 430,
    "question": "cambio",
    "questionDetails": "El cambio de un nómada a una sociedad agrícola.",
    "answer": "change, shift, switch",
    "answerDetails": "The change from a nomadic to an agricultural society."
  },
  {
    "id": 431,
    "question": "loco",
    "questionDetails": "Javier está loco por Susana. No aguanta estar sin ella.",
    "answer": "crazy, mad, insane",
    "answerDetails": "Javier is crazy about Susana. He can’t bear to be without her."
  },
  {
    "id": 432,
    "question": "saben",
    "questionDetails": "De acuerdo, gente, ya saben como funciona esto.",
    "answer": "know, aware",
    "answerDetails": "All right, people, you know how this works."
  },
  {
    "id": 433,
    "question": "sacar",
    "questionDetails": "Sacar un arma y apuntar a alguien.",
    "answer": "pull, draw",
    "answerDetails": "To pull a gun on somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 434,
    "question": "contar",
    "questionDetails": "Contar Ovejitas.",
    "answer": "count",
    "answerDetails": "To count sheep."
  },
  {
    "id": 435,
    "question": "dado",
    "questionDetails": "Algunos esquizofrénicos son dados a experimentar alucinaciones.",
    "answer": "given, certain, die",
    "answerDetails": "Some schizophrenics are given to experiencing hallucinations."
  },
  {
    "id": 436,
    "question": "último",
    "questionDetails": "Este modelo es lo último en autos de lujo.",
    "answer": "ultimate, past",
    "answerDetails": "This model is the ultimate in luxury cars."
  },
  {
    "id": 437,
    "question": "preocupes",
    "questionDetails": "No se preocupes por mí.",
    "answer": "worry",
    "answerDetails": "Do not worry on my account."
  },
  {
    "id": 438,
    "question": "pregunta",
    "questionDetails": "Su lealtad es realmente más allá de la pregunta.",
    "answer": "question",
    "answerDetails": "Her loyalty is really beyond question."
  },
  {
    "id": 439,
    "question": "otras",
    "questionDetails": "Las buenas relaciones con otras culturas son primordiales para nosotros.",
    "answer": "other, further, another",
    "answerDetails": "Good relations with other cultures is our highest priority."
  },
  {
    "id": 440,
    "question": "pronto",
    "questionDetails": "Se fueron demasiado pronto y no vieron cuando cortamos la torta.",
    "answer": "early, shortly",
    "answerDetails": "You left too early and missed the cutting of the cake."
  },
  {
    "id": 441,
    "question": "país",
    "questionDetails": "Mi padre nunca regresó al país donde nació.",
    "answer": "land, country",
    "answerDetails": "My father never returned to the land where he was born."
  },
  {
    "id": 442,
    "question": "creer",
    "questionDetails": "Su junta va a creer que eres milagrosa.",
    "answer": "think",
    "answerDetails": "Your board’s going to think you walk on water."
  },
  {
    "id": 443,
    "question": "dijiste",
    "questionDetails": "Necesitamos asegurarnos de que la estudiante de intercambio se sienta bienvenida aquí. ¿Le dijiste hola esta mañana?-Sí. Y la invité al baile.",
    "answer": "did you say, you told",
    "answerDetails": "We need to make sure that the exchange student feels welcome here. Did you say hello to her this morning?-Yes. And I invited her to the dance."
  },
  {
    "id": 444,
    "question": "hacerlo",
    "answer": "do it"
  },
  {
    "id": 445,
    "question": "ayer",
    "questionDetails": "Ayer fuimos al cine.",
    "answer": "yesterday",
    "answerDetails": "Yesterday we went to movies."
  },
  {
    "id": 446,
    "question": "cerca",
    "questionDetails": "Odio que la gente se pare cerca de mí en el tren.",
    "answer": "close",
    "answerDetails": "I hate when people stand close to me on the train."
  },
  {
    "id": 447,
    "question": "abajo",
    "questionDetails": "Ella vive 2 pisos más abajo.",
    "answer": "down, below",
    "answerDetails": "She lives two floors down."
  },
  {
    "id": 448,
    "question": "culpa",
    "questionDetails": "Fue culpa mía.",
    "answer": "fault",
    "answerDetails": "It was my fault."
  },
  {
    "id": 449,
    "question": "sabemos",
    "questionDetails": "Asi lo sabemos todo de ellas.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "Then we know everything about them."
  },
  {
    "id": 450,
    "question": "personas",
    "questionDetails": "Otras personas.",
    "answer": "people",
    "answerDetails": "Other people."
  },
  {
    "id": 451,
    "question": "llamar",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo que llamar por teléfono.",
    "answer": "call",
    "answerDetails": "I have to make a call."
  },
  {
    "id": 452,
    "question": "muerto",
    "questionDetails": "La caricatura trajo la animación de vuelta de los muertos.",
    "answer": "dead",
    "answerDetails": "The cartoon brought animation back from the dead."
  },
  {
    "id": 453,
    "question": "ganas",
    "questionDetails": "No tengo ganas de ir a cenar a un restaurante japonés.",
    "answer": "desire, eagerness",
    "answerDetails": "I have no desire to go to a Japanese restaurant for dinner."
  },
  {
    "id": 454,
    "question": "forma",
    "questionDetails": "El guión no tiene nada especial en la forma de diálogo o caracterización.",
    "answer": "way, form, shape",
    "answerDetails": "The script has nothing special in the way of dialogue or characterization."
  },
  {
    "id": 455,
    "question": "estábamos",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces, volviendo a lo que estábamos haciendo.",
    "answer": "were",
    "answerDetails": "But anyway, back to what we were doing."
  },
  {
    "id": 456,
    "question": "pedir",
    "questionDetails": "Pedir a alguien que haga algo.",
    "answer": "ask, seek",
    "answerDetails": "To ask somebody to do something."
  },
  {
    "id": 457,
    "question": "rato",
    "questionDetails": "Voy a hacer la compra. Vuelvo en un rato.",
    "answer": "bit, awhile",
    "answerDetails": "I’m going grocery shopping. I’ll be back in a bit."
  },
  {
    "id": 458,
    "question": "llamo",
    "questionDetails": "Lo llamo pasar el tiempo.",
    "answer": "call, knock",
    "answerDetails": "I call it passing the time."
  },
  {
    "id": 459,
    "question": "otros",
    "questionDetails": "Podría haber otros factores en juego.",
    "answer": "other, further, another",
    "answerDetails": "There may be other factors involved."
  },
  {
    "id": 460,
    "question": "bajo",
    "questionDetails": "Debajo de la mesa/las escaleras.",
    "answer": "under",
    "answerDetails": "Under the table/the stairs."
  },
  {
    "id": 461,
    "question": "ocho",
    "questionDetails": "Necesito dormir mis ocho horas.",
    "answer": "eight",
    "answerDetails": "Got to get my eight hours."
  },
  {
    "id": 462,
    "question": "hagas",
    "questionDetails": "Para que les hagas trucos.",
    "answer": "do, make",
    "answerDetails": "So you’ll do tricks for them."
  },
  {
    "id": 463,
    "question": "perder",
    "questionDetails": "Ella no le importaba perder una hora en la cama para ensuciar los caballos.",
    "answer": "forfeit",
    "answerDetails": "She didn’t mind forfeiting an hour in bed to muck out the horses."
  },
  {
    "id": 464,
    "question": "empezar",
    "questionDetails": "Ella había visto a Meg empezar de repente de un matorral.",
    "answer": "start",
    "answerDetails": "She had seen Meg start suddenly from a thicket."
  },
  {
    "id": 465,
    "question": "doy",
    "questionDetails": "Si te doy este libro, ¿se lo podrás dar a Phil?",
    "answer": "i give",
    "answerDetails": "If I give this book to you, will you please give it to Phil?"
  },
  {
    "id": 466,
    "question": "hacía",
    "questionDetails": "Les hacía sentirse mejor.",
    "answer": "made, did",
    "answerDetails": "Made them feel better."
  },
  {
    "id": 467,
    "question": "vuelta",
    "questionDetails": "Por favor, usa la vuelta de la hoja también.",
    "answer": "back, turn, round",
    "answerDetails": "Please use the back of the page as well."
  },
  {
    "id": 468,
    "question": "justo",
    "questionDetails": "Tiene el tamaño justo.",
    "answer": "just, right, fair",
    "answerDetails": "It’s only just big enough."
  },
  {
    "id": 469,
    "question": "bastante",
    "questionDetails": "Es bastante fuera de la cuestión.",
    "answer": "quite, pretty, rather",
    "answerDetails": "It’s quite out of the question."
  },
  {
    "id": 470,
    "question": "digas",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que me lo digas.",
    "answer": "say, tell",
    "answerDetails": "I want you to say it to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 471,
    "question": "noches",
    "questionDetails": "Algo me sucedió en esas dos noches.",
    "answer": "nights, evening",
    "answerDetails": "Something happened to me both those nights!"
  },
  {
    "id": 472,
    "question": "camino",
    "questionDetails": "La familia de todo el camino se unen en el argumento.",
    "answer": "way, road, path",
    "answerDetails": "The family from over the way were joining in the argument."
  },
  {
    "id": 473,
    "question": "llega",
    "questionDetails": "Max no está en casa. Llega a las ocho.",
    "answer": "he comes",
    "answerDetails": "Max is not home yet. He comes at 8."
  },
  {
    "id": 474,
    "question": "siquiera",
    "questionDetails": "No te puedes arriesgar, ni siquiera por mí.",
    "answer": "even",
    "answerDetails": "You cannot risk yourself, even for me."
  },
  {
    "id": 475,
    "question": "siendo",
    "questionDetails": "Parece que hoy en día puedes hacerte famoso simplemente siendo estúpido.",
    "answer": "by being",
    "answerDetails": "It seems that these days you can become a celebrity simply by being stupid."
  },
  {
    "id": 476,
    "question": "nuestros",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestros espíritus pueden comunicarse.",
    "answer": "our",
    "answerDetails": "Our spirits can commune."
  },
  {
    "id": 477,
    "question": "esté",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces con tal de que ella esté de acuerdo.",
    "answer": "is",
    "answerDetails": "Then as long as she is comfortable with it."
  },
  {
    "id": 478,
    "question": "teléfono",
    "questionDetails": "Parece haber interferencias en el teléfono.",
    "answer": "telephone",
    "answerDetails": "There seems to be some interference on her telephone."
  },
  {
    "id": 479,
    "question": "pase",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo que ver su pase.",
    "answer": "pass",
    "answerDetails": "I needto see your pass."
  },
  {
    "id": 480,
    "question": "esperar",
    "questionDetails": "Esperar a que ocurra algo.",
    "answer": "wait",
    "answerDetails": "To wait for something to happen."
  },
  {
    "id": 481,
    "question": "pensando",
    "questionDetails": "La conversación continuó, pero sus palabras me dejaron pensando.",
    "answer": "thinking, figuring, wondering",
    "answerDetails": "The conversation continued, but his words left me thinking."
  },
  {
    "id": 482,
    "question": "paz",
    "questionDetails": "La policía debe desempeñar un papel crucial en mantener la paz.",
    "answer": "peace, la paz",
    "answerDetails": "The police must play a crucial role in keeping the peace."
  },
  {
    "id": 483,
    "question": "dejó",
    "answer": "it left"
  },
  {
    "id": 484,
    "question": "cuerpo",
    "questionDetails": "El camino tomado por el cuerpo que cae.",
    "answer": "body, corps",
    "answerDetails": "The path taken by the falling body."
  },
  {
    "id": 485,
    "question": "realidad",
    "questionDetails": "Se niega a enfrentar la realidad.",
    "answer": "reality, fact",
    "answerDetails": "He refuses to face reality."
  },
  {
    "id": 486,
    "question": "número",
    "questionDetails": "El número de personas afectadas sigue siendo pequeña.",
    "answer": "number, issue, size",
    "answerDetails": "The number of people affected remains small."
  },
  {
    "id": 487,
    "question": "sentido",
    "questionDetails": "Recobrar el conocimiento or sentido.",
    "answer": "sense, meaning, respect",
    "answerDetails": "To come to one’s senses."
  },
  {
    "id": 488,
    "question": "niño",
    "questionDetails": "¿Van a tener 1 niño o una niña?",
    "answer": "boy",
    "answerDetails": "Are they going to have a boy or a girl?"
  },
  {
    "id": 489,
    "question": "quedó",
    "questionDetails": "Por eso se quedó atrás.",
    "answer": "stayed, remained, stood",
    "answerDetails": "That is why you stayed behind."
  },
  {
    "id": 490,
    "question": "espero",
    "questionDetails": "¿Esperas que tu equipo gane la liga?-Lo espero, desde luego.",
    "answer": "i expect so",
    "answerDetails": "Do you expect your team to win the league?-I expect so, of course."
  },
  {
    "id": 491,
    "question": "mierda",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Mierda! Dejé las llaves adentro del coche.",
    "answer": "crap, shitty, turd",
    "answerDetails": "Crap! I left my keys in the car."
  },
  {
    "id": 492,
    "question": "cree",
    "answer": "he thinks"
  },
  {
    "id": 493,
    "question": "mujeres",
    "questionDetails": "La bebida y las mujeres lo destruyeron.",
    "answer": "women",
    "answerDetails": "Drink and women destroyed him."
  },
  {
    "id": 494,
    "question": "estabas",
    "questionDetails": "¿Estabas manejando cuando me llamaste?-No Lo haré de nuevo.",
    "answer": "were you, you were",
    "answerDetails": "Were you driving when you called me?-I won’t do it again."
  },
  {
    "id": 495,
    "question": "mil",
    "questionDetails": "Miles de personas se congregaron delante de las Naciones Unidas para manifestar su apoyo.",
    "answer": "thousand",
    "answerDetails": "Thousands of people gathered in front of the United Nations to demonstrate their support."
  },
  {
    "id": 496,
    "question": "fueron",
    "questionDetails": "Claro que conozco a Alicia y Ryan. Fueron mis vecinos durante 5 años.",
    "answer": "they were",
    "answerDetails": "Of course I know Alicia and Ryan. They were my neighbors for five years."
  },
  {
    "id": 497,
    "question": "pone",
    "questionDetails": "¿Por qué le pones tanta azúcar al té?",
    "answer": "do you take",
    "answerDetails": "Why do you take so much sugar with your tea?"
  },
  {
    "id": 498,
    "question": "demás",
    "questionDetails": "Algunas sillas están en el jardín y las demás en la cocina.",
    "answer": "other, everyone else, remaining",
    "answerDetails": "Some chairs are in the garden and the others are in the kitchen."
  },
  {
    "id": 499,
    "question": "ejemplo",
    "questionDetails": "Seguir el ejemplo de alguien.",
    "answer": "example, instance",
    "answerDetails": "To follow somebody’s example."
  },
  {
    "id": 500,
    "question": "decía",
    "questionDetails": "A papá le gustaba bromear con mis amigos. Les decía las cosas más graciosas.",
    "answer": "he would say, i told, it said",
    "answerDetails": "Dad liked to tease my friends. He would say the funniest things to them."
  }
]
